-
-=
-= L
-= LU
-= LUO
-= LUO M
-= LUO MA
-= LUO MAD
-= LUO MADE
-= LUO MADE D
-= LUO MADE DV
-= LUO MADE DVD
-= LUO MADE DVD =
-= LUO MADE DVD =-
霏霏你好
Hello Faye!
你好嗎？
Are you good?
巴黎好嗎？
Paris are good?
我為你學法文
I learn French for you!
我好想跟你一起住在巴黎
I want to live with Paris in you.
可是我沒有錢
But money I do not have.
巴黎是愛情的世界
Paris is world of love.
沒有你 台北好寂寞
Without you Taipei is very sad.
好寂寞 好寂寞
Very very sad.
我跟爸爸和媽媽一起工作
Work with my father and my mother.
一天過一天 我的生活都是一樣
Day after day, my life is same.
我一直想到你
I always think of you.
想我們兩個走在巴黎的街頭
Imagine us on the streets of Paris.
你是我的幸福
You are my happiness.
你永遠...
You are...
呵 反正我還有在每天練習
Anyway, I'm still practicing everyday.
希望可以有機會跟你講一講
Hope I have a chance to speak
to you soon.
那... 就等你有空
So...call me back when you can.
再打電話給我好了
Okay, that's all for now.
Ok 就這樣
Bye-bye.
月色照在
The moonlight shines...
三線路
On an open road...
風吹微微
A breeze is blowing...
等待的人那沒來
I wait for him..., but he's not there.
心內真可疑
But my heart doesn't know...
想抹出彼個人
If he is coming.
說起來有點可笑
It sounds ridiculous
不過
But really...
我很久沒有這種感覺了
I haven't felt like this in a long time.
這個女孩子讓我知道 什麼叫做戀愛
This woman has brought love back
into my life.
你想想看
Think about it.
以前啊 就是這樣收保護費
All this other stuff: Protection...
三七仔
Prostitution...
詐賭啦
Gambling...
不然就是藥頭給人放高利貸
Running numbers, loan-sharking...
這哪有什麼意思？
It's all meaningless to me now.
豹哥啊
Brother Bao.
你這種情形
I think you might be having...
就是人家在說的中年危機
Some kind of mid-life crisis.
你有去過海南島嗎？
You ever been to Hainan Island?
沒去過
Never.
那你去海南島是要做什麼
What are you going to do there?
陪她好好過下半生
Enjoy life with her.
一起慢慢變老
And grow old together.
噢... 南海姑娘
Oh, my South China Sea Girl.
何必太過悲傷
Don't be so brokenhearted!
您娘啦
Fuck off.
不過 豹哥啊
But Brother Bao...
你那間房屋仲介公司 不是做得好好的？
Your real estate company
is making good money.
公司是賺錢沒有錯
Yeah, it's doing well.
大家都知道
Everyone knows that.
但是 那個是非常乾淨的
And it's clean.
若後面這條
But this other score...
我如果處理得好
If we take care of that...
就真的快活啦
Then I'm set!
豹哥
Brother Bao...
你真的確定你要這麼做？
Are you sure about this?
唉 你到我這歲數你就知道了
When you get to my age...
歡喜就好
You just want to be happy.
您娘咧
Fuck off.
我不懂
I don't understand.
不好意思 借過一下
Excuse me, sorry.
這裡可不是圖書館
This isn't a library you know.
只是隨便翻一翻而已
I'm just flipping through this.
可是我每天都看你來這
But you're here every night.
那你幹嘛不買？
Why don't you just buy it?
沒有 就有點無聊
I don't know. I guess I'm just bored.
那你還真無聊
You must be really bored.
噢
Yeah.
我不是在笑你噢
I'm not making fun of you.
只是 我每天都在這裡看到你
It's just that I see you in here a lot.
噢
Oh.
那... 明天見
Anyway, see you tomorrow.
噢 好啊
Oh, okay.
霏霏你好
Hello Faye.
你還好嗎？
How are you?
好久都沒有跟你講到話了
I haven't spoken to you in a while.
如果可以的話
If you get a chance
還是打個電話給我好嗎？
Can you give me a call back?
你永遠在我的心裡
You're always in my heart.
晚安 我的小蝴蝶
Good night, my little butterfly.
現在那四間都是...
About those four units...
大直那四間三十坪左右的
Right, four units,
each 300 square meters.
都請銀行估好價了
I had them appraised already.
下禮拜二禮拜四會有五個客戶
I start showing them next week.
一次把它看完
It's all taken care of.
很好啊
Very good.
二伯 房地產那邊你不用擔心啦
Uncle, I got a handle
on the real estate stuff.
其實我絕對有能力做更多的事情
But there are other things
I'm capable of.
小凱啊！ 這面拿去給豹哥
Kai, take this to Brother Bao.
噢
Oh.
你在發什麼呆啊
Are you asleep?
沒有啊
I'm fine.
所以啊 你另外一邊要是有缺...
If there's anything I can help with...
豹哥
Brother Bao.
小凱 你最近常在這啊
Kai, you're around a lot these days.
噢 沒有啊！ 就來幫忙
Oh yeah, just helping out.
只是暫時的
It's temporary.
這樣子啊
I see.
其實我們那邊也很需要大學生
Actually,
we could use a smart college boy.
沒有 豹哥 我自己有在計劃
It's okay, I've got plans already.
嗯 你如果有什麼需要的話
Well, if you need anything....
儘管跟我講啊
Just let me know.
不要客氣
Don't be shy.
好 謝謝豹哥
Sure. Thanks, Brother Bao..
很好吃啊？
Enjoying that?
嗯
Uh-huh.
來 祝你得大獎啊        好 謝謝
-Good luck. -Thanks.
再來啊        一定會的
-Come again. -Sure.
阿桑 我要買一張刮刮樂
Ma'am, I'd like to buy a scratcher.
你要哪一種的？
Sure, what kind?
一張旺旺來 一張金包銀好了
One "Dream Come True".
One "Treasure Chest".
好
Okay.
祝你得大獎喔
The fortune god wishes you luck.
財神爺最近好像都不太理我
He hasn't been much help lately.
怎麼會
No way.
你就是要常常來刮
Come play more often.
財神爺他認識你 要中獎就很容易啊
And he'll take good care of you.
幹什麼麥走
Hey! Come back here!
死孩子
Thugs!
麥走
Come back!
你沖啥你
I'm going to get you!
頭髮... 頭髮亂了
Watch the hair!
你這死小孩
You little thugs!
走走走
Running away!
好膽麥走！ 麥走
Come back here!
麥走
Come back!
我不懂
I don't understand.
你都在看什麼書啊？
What are you reading?
就看這個啊
Just this.
嗯
Oh.
他這上面都有音標可以照著念
It's got a pronunciation guide.
所以 你自己看書學法文喔？
So... you're teaching yourself French?
嗯 對啊
Yeah.
有用嗎？
Is it working?
好像沒有
I'm not sure.
那你應該要再去找其他的方法
Maybe you should try something else.
霏霏你好
Hello Faye.
發生什麼事了嗎？
Is something wrong?
為什麼都沒有打電話給我
Why haven't you called me?
我只是想知道你好不好而已啊
I just want to know that you're okay.
我好想你
I miss you so much.
我好愛你
I love you so much.
再見
Goodbye.
您娘咧
Fuck off!
不要跑        給我站住啊
-Don't run! -Freeze!
不要跑
Hey, don't run!
干！ 沖啥啦
Fuck, what are you doing?
不要抓 不要抓
Hey, be careful!
笑屁啊！ 弄他啦
Let's get the little prick!
人來了 人來了
Someone's coming.
請問需要幫忙嗎？
How may I help you?
賽您娘啦
Fuck you.
順利嗎？
Did it go smoothly?
有狀況啦
I ran into some problems.
怎樣？ 皮條喔？
What? Cops?
東西我先藏起來 不會讓他們找到
I hid it. It's safe.
欸 我下半生涼涼就靠這
Hey, this is my retirement fund.
阿洪 幹嘛？
What is it, Hong?
沒有啊 我只是想說
Nothing. I just...
沒事的話我先回去了
If there's nothing else I'm going home.
你在外面等我一下
Wait for me outside.
好
Okay.
二伯 那個人是誰？
Uncle, who was that?
阿洪 我跟你講啊
Listen, Hong.
我呢就準備退休了
I'm getting ready to retire
所以我打算這邊以後就交給你了
And I've decided to leave
all this to you.
沒問題啊 二伯
No problem, Uncle.
像那個什麼彩券行那種啊
But this lottery store shit...
沒水準的事以後就別幹了
It's beneath you. Cut it out.
知道嗎？
Understand?
可是二伯 你也知道
But Uncle, you know...
我們那一票真的幹得很漂亮
It was a real sweet score!
這邊賺的全部給你
Everything here could be yours.
幹嘛？ 嫌少啊？
That's not enough?
不是 我只是想 有時候需要趣味趣味
It's just that...
I want to see a little action.
趣味？
Action?
好 我知道了
Okay, I understand.
你不用再說服我了
Say no more.
清楚了？
So we're clear?
清楚了
We're clear.
清楚就好
Good.
看什麼看？
What are you looking at?
沒有啊
Nothing.
嘿 小凱
Hey, Kai.
嘿 高
Hey, Gao.
謝啦
Thanks.
那桃子今天也在嗎？
So was Peach there tonight?
在啊
Yeah.
然後咧？
And?
噢 我們噢
Oh, we...
我有在那個啦
I'm working on it.
嗯
Oh.
怎麼啦？
What's wrong?
嗯 沒事啊
Nothing.
你還餓不餓？
You still hungry?
餓啊
Yeah.
噢
Okay.
你的幸福
To your happiness!
現在你跟我回去
Come with me now.
我把這的卒仔處理掉之後
I'll take care of this bastard first.
麥啦
No!
曼曼...
Mandy...
為什麼你要這樣對待我？
How could you do this to me?
差不多可以準備吃囉
Dinner's almost ready.
基永
Ji-Yong.
你剛剛說什麼
What did you say?
我說可以準備吃了
I said dinner's ready.
可是我要出去了耶
But I'm heading out.
喔
Okay.
喂 好 我馬上下去
Hello? I'll be right down.
吳興在樓下了
Wushing's downstairs.
嗯
Oh.
那我走囉
Okay, I'm going then.
他們全部都穿那個西裝
They were all wearing suits.
他們穿那個什麼色？ 啊！ 橘子色
The color? Orange.
大家看起來都很英俊 一表人才的樣子
The were all quite handsome and polite.
一個人進來就跟我說要買
One of them said they wanted to buy one.
就在那邊刮刮刮 我也沒去注意
And started scratching.
I was distracted.
然後就砰一下...
And there was a...
老闆娘 你放心 我們會處理的
Don't worry, Ma'am.
We'll take care of it.
謝謝
Thank you.
沒有啦！ 我還沒說完啦
Wait, I'm not done yet.
下次再有這樣的案子 麻煩你捅死我
Next time we get a case like this,
just shoot me.
肚子餓不餓？
Are you hungry?
去找東西吃
Let's grab something to eat.
好啊 學長
Okay, sir.
長江一號
Jack-knife one. Over.
學長 你真的覺得會有人回來嗎？
Sir, do you think they'll really
come back?
啊不然咧？
You can count on it.
我們這不是加槓的
It's the big time for us.
對厚
All right.
欸...
Here.
喂？
Hello?
我現在在工作 晚點打給你
I'm working. Call you back later.
學長 你女朋友喔？
Sir, was that your girlfriend?
啊？
Huh?
你女朋友啊        啊？
-Your girlfriend? -Huh?
妹啦
Your chick?
關你什麼事啊？
None of your business.
喔
Oh.
其中之一啦
It was just one of them!
而且我告訴你 像我們這一種
And I'm telling you, guys like us...
要妹多得數不完
We get all the chicks.
真的喔？
Really?
多學著點
Watch and learn.
好
Okay.
專心工作
Stay focused.
是
Okay.
誰回來拿 我們就把他抓起來
Whoever comes back, we'll grab them.
嘿
Hey.
嗨
Hi.
你有沒有想要去上課啊？
Hey, have you thought taking
some classes?
喔
Um...
我覺得那樣應該會學比較快
I think it might be faster.
像我就在學跳舞喔
I'm taking dance classes right now.
你有聽過LindyHop嗎？
Have you ever heard of the Lindy Hop?
什麼啊？
The what?
就是一種搖擺舞
It's a type of swing dance.
不然 我跳給你看喔
Um...maybe I can just show you.
大概是這樣
It goes something like this...
類似的
Something like that.
呵
Oh.
他們那邊也有一些語言課
Hey, that have some
language classes there.
像是英文 日文...
English, Japanese...
應該也有法文
They should have French too.
不然下次我幫你拿一張課表
I can get you a schedule.
沒關係啦
That's okay.
是喔
Really...
你是不是要去法國啊
Hey, so are you going to France
or something?
對啊
Yeah.
真的喔？
Really?
我女朋友現在在那邊
My girlfriend's over there.
喔
Oh.
所以你為你的女朋友 然後學法文？
So you're studying French
for your girlfriend?
喔
Oh.
這樣很浪漫
That sounds romantic.
會嗎？
Really?
她不這樣覺得嗎？
Doesn't she think so?
嗯
Yeah.
喂？
Hello?
霏霏啊 嘿
Faye? Hi.
怎樣？ 你最近還好嗎
How have you been?
嗯
Oh.
喔
所以 都還Ok嗎？
So, is everything okay?
喔？
Oh
我喔 我還Ok啊
Me? I'm doing okay.
對啊 沒什麼事
Nothing much.
怎麼了嗎？
What is it?
嗯
Oh.
為什麼？
Why?
你是怎麼搞的啦？
What's wrong with you?
家裡沒這個錢啦
We don't have the money for that.
我會還你們的啦
I'll pay you guys back.
你在想什麼啦 年輕人？
What are you thinking, kid?
我知道 可是我就是要趕快過去啊
I don't know...
I just need to get over there.
算了啦！ 真的算了啦
Forget about it! Just forget about it.
說不定這樣對你比較好
Maybe this is all for the best.
再想一想啦
Think about it.
或許去外面找一個工作做
or why don't you go get a job?
我跟你老爸也沒有冀望你在這裡幫忙啊
We're not forcing you to work here.
對不對
Right?
我來收 你們先上去沒關係
I'll close up.
You guys can to upstairs.
不要想那麼多
Don't dwell on it too much.
你需要多少？
How much do you need?
只要夠去巴黎就可以了
Just enough to get to Paris.
可能還需要在那邊多待一陣子
And maybe to stay out there for a while.
那沒有問題
Not a problem.
只是突然就這樣
It's just that...
我們本來都已經講好了
We had already made these plans.
別跟我解釋這一些
No need to explain.
感情本來就是這個樣子
That's the way love goes.
以後你習慣就好了
You'll figure it out.
豹哥 謝謝
Thanks, Brother Bao
我去你家吃麵都吃這麼多年了
How long have I been eating
at your restaurant?
你 我信得過
I know you're good for it.
唉 年輕不懂珍惜 都錯過了
Ah...the one that got away...
其實談談小戀愛還不錯的
It's nice to be in love, isn't it?
學長
Sir...
我們這次這個案子 有沒有機會開到槍啊
Do you think we'll get to use our guns
this time?
呵 學長 我一定可以的
I can handle it, sir.
你說啊
What is it?
啥？
What?
好 我知道
Okay, I understand.
你等在那不要動 我來處理
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
叫你回去你就回去
I said get out of here!
小凱 你要去哪裡啊？
Kai, where are you going?
喔！ 今天可能有點事 不能幫忙了
Oh,I have some stuff to do.
I can't work tonight.
等一下就回來了
I'll be back later.
你來這幹嘛？
Hey, what are you here?
我找豹哥
I'm here to see Brother Bao.
找豹哥喔？
Brother Bao?
他叫我來的
He told me to come by.
嗯
Oh.
確定沒有事情要幫忙？
Sure you don't need help with anything?
我還好 謝謝
I'm okay. Thanks.
二伯 他找你
Uncle, he's here to see you.
你沒事吧？
Don't you have something to do?
喔 我約了人看房子
Oh, I have an apartment to show.
那我先去囉
I better get going.
來 坐吧 坐吧
Come, have a seat.
都準備好了嗎？
So are you all set?
差不多了
Yeah, just about.
好
Good.
我還有個小事要請你幫忙
I have a little favor I need
to ask of you.
喔 好
Oh, okay..
麻煩你一下 就是呢
Sorry to trouble you.
我有個小東西要帶過去
I need you to take something with you.
喔 好
Okay, okay.
豹哥 那... 那個東西呢？
Uh...Brother Bao, where is it?
啊！ 要你幫我去拿一下
Oh, I need you to pick it up for me.
喔！ 沒問題
Oh, okay. Sure.
別擔心 都安排好了
Don't worry, it's all taken care of.
到時候就有人把東西交給你了
Someone will give it to you.
這東西非常的重要
This package is very important to me.
你最好給我好好的處理
So you better be careful.
知道嗎？
Got it?
嗯
Yeah.
你現在應該很興奮啊？
You must be very excited.
嗯 對啊 對啊
Oh, yeah.
但是豹哥
But Brother Bao...
怎麼啦？
What is it?
我不知道 我只是
It's just...I don't know...
那個... 你機票訂好了沒有？ 小凱
Hey, is your flight all set, Kai?
喔 對啊！ 明天早上
Yeah, I leave tomorrow morning.
要不要多帶一點錢？
Do you need some extra cash?
不用 不用 夠了
No, I have enough.
好
Good.
歡迎光臨
Hello and welcome.
嘿 桃子
Hey, Peach.
嗯
Huh?
嗯 那個
Do you...
什麼？
What?
你知道我們後面還有這個嗎？
Do you know if we have more
of these in stock?
我不知道 你去後面看看啊
I don't know. Go check in back
喔 好啊
Oh, okay.
謝謝
Thanks.
不會
No problem.
歡迎光臨
Hello and welcome.
嘿 高
Hey, Gao.
嘿
Hey.
我準備差不多了
So I'm just about set.
我只是過來跟你說一聲
I just came over to say bye
好啊！ 那走啊
Okay, let's go.
要去哪？
Go where?
吃飯啊
To eat.
不用 不用 真的不用
That's okay, really.
我待會還有一點事啊
I have some stuff to take care of.
你都要走了
But you're leaving.
嘿 桃子
Hey, Peach.
我們一兩個小時後就回來Ok嗎？
We'll be back in an hour or so.
Is that okay?
喔
Oh.
我只等兩個小時喔
I only have two hours.
看吧！ 沒問題啦
See? No problem.
好啦！ 可我待會要拿個東西
Okay.
But I have to go pick something up first.
好啊
Okay.
你們看看
Look guys...
現在有什麼好處
He has this score...
他竟然也沒想要分給我們
And he's cutting us out of it.
我們不是兄弟嗎
Aren't we brothers?
一天到晚叫我們來賣什麼小公寓
Instead he has us showing
shitty apartments all day.
豹哥 已經差不多了
Brother Bao is almost finished anyway.
真的不用怕
There's nothing to worry about.
萬一出了什麼事 統統推到那個小子身上去
If anything happens,
the kid takes the blame.
我們幹一票 還有人當替死鬼 多好
We make a sweet score,
someone else takes the fall.
你們不是也想要幹一票大的嗎？
Don't you guys want to make a big score?
現在機會來啦
Here's your chance!
鄭先生 鄭太太
Mr. and Ms. Cheng...
不好意思
Excuse us.
你們還滿意嗎？
What do you think?
其實我們上一個房客 也非常喜歡這裡
Actually, our last tenants
really loved this place.
只是後來那位先生不小心偷吃
But the husband got caught cheating.
然後他還有外過...
Things got messy and...
我們過兩天 再幫你們裝洗衣機還有烘乾機
We can install your new washer
and dryer in a few days.
我們大概還要再考慮一下
We'd like to think about it some more.
明智 明智
Very wise, very wise.
其實這樣的條件 這樣的價錢
But I can assure you
for a place like this.
真的很實在
The price is quite reasonable.
這是我的名片
Here's my card.
您看有什麼需要 再打上面電話給我就好
If you need anything,
don't hesitate to call.
好好好
Okay.
謝謝
Thanks.
土炮啦
Morons.
反正我人會一直待在豹哥旁邊
Anyway, I'll be with Brother Bao.
這樣他就不會懷疑
That way he won't suspect anything.
你們一拿到東西呢
Once you make the grab
就去你阿姨家
Bring it your aunt's place.
我再跟你們會合
I'll meet up with you guys there.
還有 還有
One more thing...
水喔？
Sweet, eh?
水啦
Sweet!
學長 你要不要來一片？
Sir, do you want a piece?
我不餓
I'm not hungry.
學長！ 這真的很好吃
But sir, it's really good.
我說不餓了
I said I'm not hungry.
學長 你確定？
Sir, are you sure?
呃
Oh.
學長 你看
Sir, look!
吳興 你在幹嘛？ 快點啦
Wushing, move it!
小凱
Hey, Kai.
暗號
Password.
暗號啦
呵？
Huh?
暗號啦！
Password!
是那個豹哥他叫我來拿個東西...
Brother Bao told me to come
pick up something...
你沒有把東西交給我
If you don't give me what I need...
我怎麼把東西交給你啦？
How can I give you what you need?
暗號啦
Password.
可是我...
But I...
我跟你開玩笑的啦
I'm just messing with you.
你怎麼那麼古椎
Don't be such a dipshit.
拿好喔
Be careful with this.
就這樣啊？
This is it?
啊！ 學長 我們怎麼辦？
What should we do, sir?
追啊
Follow them!
嘿 高
Hey, Gao.
好了 走吧
Let's go.
拿到了嗎？
Did you get it?
拿到了 沒問題啦
Yeah, no problem.
借看一下啦
Let me see it.
不要 你很土
You can't handle it.
快點啦
Come on!
不要 現在就是 我有Gun你沒Gun 怎麼樣
No way,
it's my gun, not your gun...got it?
拜託好不好？        不要啦
-Please? -No.
好了 去吃吧
Okay, let's eat
喔
Okay.
那我們要從哪邊開始？
Where do you want to start?
你決定
You decide
好啊
Okay.
那你去巴黎要先幹嘛？
So...what are you going to do
when you get to Paris?
去把霏霏追回來啊
Get Faye back.
前面水煎包還蠻好吃的
Those dumplings are pretty good.
是喔
Okay.
幹嘛？
What is it?
喔 沒有
Nothing.
認識嗎？
Do you know her?
算吧
Sort of.
好啊
Okay.
等一下
Hey, wait...
嗨
Hi.
好幾天沒看到你
I haven't seen you around recently.
對啊 最近比較忙
Yeah, I've been a little busy.
嗯
Oh.
喔 對了
Oh yeah...
我前幾天去上跳舞課的時候
I was at dance class the other day.
有順便幫你看了一下
And I checked it out for you.
他們的法文課好像是在...
I think they do have French classes...
沒關係啦！ 因為我要去巴黎了
It's okay. I'm going to Paris.
是喔 什麼時候啊？
Really? When?
喔 明天早上
Um, tomorrow morning.
喔
Oh.
我們想說以後可能沒機會了
I probably won't get this tood
for a while.
所以... 就趕快來這邊吃一吃
So I better eat it while I can.
對啊 要不要再吃一點東西
Do you want to get something to eat?
喔 這是高高
Oh, this is Gao.
這是...
This is...
我是蘇西
I'm Susie.
她在那個... 書店工作
She, um, works at the bookstore.
你們幫我多買幾個
Can you guys get me some dumplings?
我去那邊買大腸包小腸
I'm going to go get a sausage roll.
喔
Oh.
你一個人啊？
So are you here alone?
嗯 等一下要去上課
Yeah, I'm just on my way to class.
你好像很常上很多課的樣子
Seems like you take a lot of classes.
就是想讓自己忙一點
I like to keep myself busy.
嗯
Oh.
先生 不要插隊好嗎
Please don't cut in line.
歹勢喔！ 你跟我們來一下
Excuse me. You're coming with us.
我們等一下就回來
We'll be right back.
你們要幹嘛？
What do you want?
東西在你那邊        交出來啦
-Do you have it? -Hand it over.
我不知道你們在講什麼
I don't know what you're talking about.
讓他看看啦
Show him what we're packing
不要跑 警察
Don't run, Police!
不要跑
Don't run!
你剛剛跑去哪？
Hey, where did you go?
快一點 快
Hurry, hurry!
走啦
Come on.
站住
Stand still!
搞什麼啦！
What's wrong with you?
沒有 我只是想說
Nothing, I was just thinking...
那邊人太多了 就不要在那邊
It was a little too crowded over there.
你是不是在躲誰啊？
Are you running from someone?
沒有啊
No.
干
Fuck.
現在怎麼辦？
What now?
嘿 那是不是他朋友？
Hey, isn't that his friend?
你是不是在躲剛才那兩個人？
Are you hiding from those two guys?
沒有 我根本不認識
No, I don't even know who they are.
那我走囉
Right. I'll see you later.
等一下
Wait a second.
幹嘛？
What?
沒有 我們可以在這邊等一下
Let's just hang out here for now.
那高高呢？
What about Gao?
你最好給我乖一點 竹竿
Just be cool, Stretch!
走啦        喔
-Let's go. -Oh.
高高
Gao!
幹嘛？
What?
不好意思 借過一下
Excuse us. Coming through.
不好意思
Excuse us.
發生什麼事了？
What's going on?
高高
Gao.
不好意思 借過一下
Excuse us, sorry.
我們要去哪？
Where are we going?
干 你閉嘴啦！ 進去
Shut the fuck up and get in.
他們是誰啊？
Who were those guys?
就...
They're...uh...
你朋友是不是被他們抓走？
Was your friend just kidnapped?
沒有啊
No.
你要幹嘛？
What are you doing?
我要報警
Calling the police.
喔
Oh.
等一下 不能報警啦
Wait, you can't do that!
為什麼？
Why not?
這應該不是什麼大問題啦
I'm sure it's just a misunderstanding.
真的不行啦
Seriously, don't do that.
你是不是知道什麼啊？
What's this all about?
我不知道啊
I don't know.
好啦！ 你打嘛
Fine. Go ahead and call.
喂 不好意思 我要報警
Hello, please connect me to the police.
等一下 真的不行啦
Hey, please don't do that.
好啦！ 等一下 你聽我講嘛
Hold on, listen to me.
可能是因為這個啦
Maybe it have something to do with this.
你聽我解釋嘛
Let me explain.
好好好 你說
Okay. Explain.
去皇家喔？        嗯
-Back to the Palace? -Yeah .
那他呢？
What about him?
喔 我在這邊下車就好了
Oh, you can just drop me off here.
唉唷 我肚子好餓喔
I'm hungry.
你們肚子都不餓的喔
Aren't you guys hungry?
餓啊 可是這邊有什麼好吃的嗎？
Yeah, but is there anything good
around here?
我怎麼知道？
How would I know?
我知道前面有一間還不錯的水餃店
I know a pretty good
dumpling place nearby.
我也不知道啦
I don't know, okay?
反正我就是想說 這樣可以去巴黎找我女朋友
I'm just trying to get to Paris
to see my girlfriend.
那東西哪裡來的？
Well, where did the package come from?
是別人叫我幫他拿的啦
I was picking it up for someone.
誰？
Who?
豹哥啊
Brother Bao.
他借我錢讓我可以去巴黎的
I'm borrowed some money
from him to get to Paris.
豹哥？
Brother Bao?
嗯 我真的沒辦法嘛
Yeah. I was desperate.
我也不知道他跟那些人有什麼關係
I don't know how he's involved
in all this.
那他是幹嘛的啊？
Well what does he do?
房地產
Real estate.
好啦 我現在打給他
Okay, I'll try calling him.
哈 騙肖
I don't buy it!
我來
I'll get it.
喂
Hello?
喂 請問豹哥在嗎？
Hello, may I speak to Brother Bao?
請問哪裡找？
May I ask who's speaking?
我是小凱 我有急事要找豹哥
This is Kai. It's kind of urgent.
是啊 是啊 有什麼事嗎？
Of course, how can I help you?
呃 不是 我有點事情要跟他講
Oh, no. I just really need
to talk to him.
請問你知道他什麼時候回來嗎？
Do you know when he'll be back?
可是我東西現在沒有帶在身上
I don't have that information
on me right now.
不是 我有急事要找他
But...I really need to speak to him.
好啦 好啦 不然你把資料直接寄給我
I'll tell you what...
go ahead and send me a brochure.
好 再聯絡
Okay, let's keep in touch.
喂
Hello?
詐騙集團
Credit-card scam.
豹哥好像在忙
I think Brother Bao is busy.
所以呢？
So?
不知道
I don't know.
那我們把他打開看看
Let's just open it.
不行啦        我看一下
-No -Let me see it.
這裡面是什麼啊？
What's in here?
不知道
I don't know.
不覺得很奇怪嗎？
Don't you think it's a little strange?
不知道什麼就隨便答應別人
You have no idea what you're delivering.
你到底在想什麼啊？
What were you thinking?
怎麼啦？
What is it?
那個人
That guy.
你認識嗎？        不認識啊
-You recognize him? -No.
警察
Police!
他在喊什麼啊？
What is he yelling about?
不知道
I don't know
你們兩個
You two!
怎麼辦？
-What should we do? -Run!
喂
Hey!
等我
Hey, wait for me!
快
Hurry!
你們兩個不要跑
You two, stop!
站住
Stop!
快點啦
Hurry!
好啦
Okay!
我是警察
I'm a police officer!
不好意思 不好意思
Excuse me.
同學 捷運站內禁止奔跑喔
Kids, no running in the subway!
先生 捷運站內禁止奔跑
Sir, no running in the subway!
我們好像甩掉他了
Hey, I think we ditched him.
那很好啊
Yeah, great.
你要去哪啊？
Hey, where are you going?
(The Palace)
出來
Get out!
我 謝豪一定會一輩子疼惜曼曼
I, Howard, promise I
will also love Mandy!
永遠都不變心
That will never change!
我 曼曼
I, Mandy...
一輩子都不會離開謝豪
Will be with Howard forever!
阿姨 我們上去囉
Auntie, we're going upstairs.
嗯 嗯
Oh.
干！ 這真的很好吃耶
Fuck! These are pretty good.
我們還要等多久啊
How much longer do we have to wait?
沒那麼快 還要等一下
A little while, just sit tight.
對不起
I'm sorry
我真的不知道 現在到底怎麼一回事
I don't know what's going on either.
我不懂你為什麼把自己搞成這樣
How did you get yourself involved
in this?
我不知道 我只是想去巴黎而已
I don't know, I was just trying to
get to Paris.
就這樣啊
That's all.
但是真的有必要弄成這樣嗎？
You couldn't think of an easier way?
我那時候也覺得還好啊！
It seemed reasonable at the time.
我想也是
I'm sure it did.
現在怎麼辦？
What now?
高高怎麼辦？
What about Gao?
小凱
Kai...
那裡
This way!
快點啊
Hurry!!
警察！ 不要跑
Police! Stop running!
快點
Hurry!
快 這邊 這邊
This way!
糟糕
Oh shit.
幹嘛？
What are you doing?
快跳 不然會被發現
Dance or we're going to get caught!
快點啦 跳啊
Come on! Dance!
好啦
Okay.
不是那樣跳啦
You're doing it wrong.
有差嗎？        有
-Does it matter? -Yes
往前
Forward.
你跳你的
Worry about yourself.
像這樣啊
Like this.
這裡
Here.
他去哪啊
Hey, where is he going?
應該可以走了吧
I think we can go now.
喔 好啊
Oh, okay.
先生 你是不是認錯人了...
Sir, I think you have the wrong person.
二伯 我要去帶客人了
Uncle, I have an apartment to show.
現在？ 三更半夜了
Now? This late?
很難款待
It was difficult to schedule.
客人說現在才有空
This is the only time they
were available.
那我先去囉
I better get going!
快來不及了
I don't want to be late.
剛剛跳的不錯
Nice moves back there.
很醜吧！ 對不對？
Pretty bad right?
是有進步的空間啦
There's room for improvement.
現在呢？
So what now?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我不知道你為什麼那麼急著要過去
Why you need to get
over there so badly?
你不是說她在那裡等你嗎？
Didn't you say that
she's waiting for you?
嗯 對啊！ 是吧
Yeah. I guess so.
其實 她根本不知道我要過去
Actually,
she doesn't even know I'm coming.
你在開玩笑吧？
You're kidding, right?
我們那時候就有說好 要一起去巴黎
We talked about going to Paris together.
然後呢？
And then?
她可能覺得我留在台北比較好吧
I guess she decided I
should just stay in Taipei.
反正 我想說不管怎樣就先過去
I thought that if I could
get over there somehow.
至少還去過了
At least I would have that.
我待在這邊我也不知道在幹什麼
I don'thave a whole lot going
for me here.
自摸
Draw!
莊家連一拉一紅中三花混一色
Flush! Red dragon,
three seasons, mixed suits!
十台
Wiped you out!
干！ 我們又沒有拿錢
Fuck! We're not playing for money!
我剛剛就說過啦！ 我以前照三餐打的
I told you guys...I have mahjong skills.
那你穿這幹嘛？
What are you wearing?
沒啊 忘了脫了
Oh, I forgot to take it off.
你做這個沒出息啦
What a crappy job.
歡迎光臨 謝謝光臨
Hello and welcome, please come again.
你學超像的欸
Good impression.
哭爸
Shit yeah.
沒有啦 要去當兵了啦
I just got drafted though.
干
Fuck.
那你有妹嗎？
You got a girlfriend?
記得上車前要多打幾炮啦
Better hit that while you still can!
真的
For real.
沒有啦 沒有什麼妹啦
No. I don't have a girlfriend.
但是 就有在那個啦
But I'm working on it.
哪個啦？
Working on what?
Yeah what?
沒有啦
Nothing.
那妹仔是誰啊？
Who's the girl?
同事啊
Co-worker.
她叫什麼名字？
What's her name?
桃子
Peach.
喔 桃子
Oh...Peach.
桃子
Peach.
卡哇伊吶
So cute.
對啊
Yeah.
那你什麼時候要去？
How much longer do you have?
差不多了
Not much longer.
那她知道你要去當兵了嗎？
Does she know you're leaving?
不知道
No.
干 女生要是聽到這個
Fuck! When she hears that...
奶罩馬上脫下來啊
Her bra will fly right off!
真的嗎？
Really?
不然你就跟她說
Just tell her...
妹仔 我去當兵了
"Girl, I'm going off to the army..."
我只是想要讓你知道
"I want you to know..."
我會在那裡想你
"I won't stop thinking about you".
這樣就對了
That's how it's done.
對啦 這樣講就沒有問題了
Definitely. You're in. No problem.
真的嗎？
Really?
不然你以為他怎麼每次都把得到妹？
How do you think he ever gets laid?
其實我根本不用當兵
Actually, I've never even been
in the army.
媽的
Damn.
打麻將啊？
Playing mahjong?
嘿 阿洪
Hey, Hong
我也要打 誰贏？
I want to play, who's winning?
這土炮是誰？
Who's this moron?
這我們抓來的啊
We grabbed him.
東西呢？
Where's the package?
喔
Oh.
我們遇到一點狀況
We had kind of a setback.
可是在他朋友那邊
But his friend has it.
對 所以我們就想說
Right, so we were thinking...
想什麼？ 說什麼？
Who told you guys to think?
就我們先把他抓來
If we grabbed him...
你們還在野餐啊！
What is this? A picnic?
叫你們拿東西
I said get the package.
抓個土炮回來
But you bring back this moron!
我怎麼會被你們跟到啊！
I can't believe you guys are my crew.
歹勢啦 阿洪
Our bad, Hong.
對不起啦 阿洪
Yeah, sorry Hong.
對不起
Sorry, Hong.
沒關係 沒關係
It's okay, it's okay.
只要我們重新掌握到狀況
We'll just have to adapt
to the circumstances.
我們還是可以把事情順利完成
We can still make this
a successful score.
喂 高？
Hey, Gao?
喂 小凱 我是高高
Hey Kai, it's me, Gao.
我知道啊 你還好吧？
I know it's you! Are you okay?
是高高
It's Gao.
高高
Hey, Gao.
還好啊
Not bad.
你現在到底在哪裡啊？
Where are you?
喂
Hey.
我限你三十分鐘之內 把東西交給我們
You have thirty minutes
to get me the package.
啊？
Huh?
不然你就等著去河邊撈屍體喔
Or there's going to be a dead body
at bottom of the rive
屍... 體？
Dead body?
那你要我怎麼做嘛？
What do you want me to do?
永福地下道 有沒有
You know the Yongfu Bridge?
嗯
Uh-huh.
河的另外一邊
On the other side of the river.
然後你就往前走一點
So...walk forward a little bit.
然後...
And then...
再往前走一點
Walk forward a little bit more.
然後... 右邊
And then...on your right...
右邊有一塊空地
There's an empty lot on the right.
你就在那邊等我們就好了
Just wait for us there.
好好好 我馬上過去
Okay, I'll be right there.
我警告你喔 一個人來喔！ 不要報警
I'm warning you! Come alone. No cops.
不然你就要撈屍體喔
Or there will be a dead body
in the river!
好好好 我知道
Okay, I understand.
你等我一下 等我一下
Just hold on, I'll be there.
先把他綁起來啊
Tie him up now please.
喔 好啊
Oh, okay.
怎麼樣了？
What?
他們要拿高高來交換
They want to exchange the package
for Gao.
那現在怎麼辦？
What are you going to do?
我應該要先走了
I guess I should get going.
是喔！
Really?
我就自己處理好了
I guess I should take care
of this myself.
你真的要一個人去喔？
You're really going alone?
大概吧
Probably.
喂
Hey.
我在想說 兩個人一起去 會不會比較好？
I'm think it might be better
if there's two of us.
你確定要去嗎？
You sure you want to come?
可以啊
Okay.
你確定... 你Ok？
You sure you're okay?
謝謝你陪我聊那麼久
Thanks so much for listening.
跟你講話我也很開心
I'm just glad I can be here for you.
那... 就晚安囉
So...I guess this is goodnight?
晚安
Goodnight.
這是怎樣？
What is this?
基永 你怎麼會在這？
Ji-Yong, what are you doing here?
基永？
Ji-Yong?
他是誰啊？
Who is he?
我不是有留紙條給你嗎？
Didn't you see the note I left?
我看啦！ 但他是誰啊？
I saw it. But who's he?
朋友啊
A friend.
嗨！ 我是Raymond
Hi, I'm Raymond.
朋友？        欸
-A friend? -Hey.
對啊
That's right.
是嗎？
Oh yeah?
你不要那麼激動
Hey, why don't you calm down?
我沒有激動啊
I am calm!
別這樣
Don't do that!
Raymond 你還好吧？
Raymond, are you okay?
我沒事 我Ok 不用擔心我
I'm okay, no need to worry.
你幹嘛推他啊？
What did you push him for?
是他先動手的喔
He started it.
有沒有那麼嚴重啊？
I barely touched you.
我們只是聊天 沒什麼！ 就這樣而已
We were just talking, that's it.
雖然...        Raymond
-Although... -Raymond!
媛媛現在知道你不值得
Yuan finally realizes you're
not worth it
真的嗎？
Is that true?
我...
I...
媛媛 告訴他啊
Yuan, tell him.
關你什麼事啊？
Stay out of it.
對不起啦
I'm sorry!
媛媛... 等一下
Yuan, wait...
我已經跟你說過
I already told you.
我需要時間好好想一想
I need time to think things over.
媛媛
Yuan...
你手機響了
Hey, your phone's ringing.
我知道
I know.
至少我們還把高高救回來
At least I'm getting Gao back.
反正都等那麼久了
I've gotten so used to waiting.
最慘就是繼續待在這邊
I'll just be stuck here a little longer.
我覺得待在這裡也不錯啊
Being stuck here isn't so bad.
東西呢？
Where's the package?
我朋友呢？
Where's my friend?
東西呢？
Where's the package?
高高呢？
Where's Gao?
誰啦？
Who?
我朋友啊
My friend.
東西交出來喔
Hand it over.
你幹嘛？
What are you doing?
你幹嘛？ 放開她
What are you doing? Let her go!
你幹嘛？
Hey!
打我幹嘛？
Why did you hit me?
把他放開 東西拿出來啦
Leave him alone! Hand it over!
你們把東西拿出來就好啦
Just give us the package, okay?
有聽到沒？
Did you hear me?
好 你不要那麼激動啦
Okay, just take it easy.
智障
Idiot.
你打我幹什麼啦？
Why did you have to hit me?
走了啦
Let's go!
你有沒有怎樣？
Are you okay?
我鼻子斷了啦...
My nose is broken!
我看...
Let me see.
沒有斷啦
It's not broken.
可是... 等一下可能會很腫
But it will probably be swollen.
高高怎麼辦？ 東西又掉了
Gao's gone, the package is gone.
完蛋了啦
I'm finished.
你要去哪？
Hey, where are you going?
等一下啦
Wait for me!
蘇西 等我一下啦
Susie, wait for me!
你幹嘛？
What are you doing?
一定有
There has to be one!
什麼？
What?
你看
Look!
這不太好吧
That's not a good idea.
你會不會騎太快啦？
Aren't you going a little fast?
這裡處理好 大家就爽啦！
Well done, we're all set.
妥當啦
Very good.
學長 你去哪裡啦？
Sir, where have you been?
他在哪？
Where is he?
裡面
Inside.
下來
Get down.
回去皇家嗎？
Back to the Palace?
嗯
Yeah.
干 超衰的
Fuck, that was lame.
真的
Seriously.
喂
Hello?
那個小凱
Hey, uh...Kai.
那邊怎麼樣 一切順利吧？
How's everything going?
豹哥 我有打給你
Brother Bao,
I've been trying to reach you!
怎麼啦！ 那個東西拿到了嗎？
What's wrong? Did you have the package?
有！ 我有！ 可是有人在追我
Yeah, I did...but someone's after me!
他們還抓了我的朋友
They grabbed my friend too!
誰？
Who?
我不知道啊！ 他們都穿橘色的西裝
I don't know!
They were all wearing orange suits.
東西在不在你那嘛？
But you still have the package?
還在我這邊啊！
Yeah...I still have it.
可是他們...        好好好 我跟你講
-But they... -Okay, listen to me.
你就聽我的話 乖乖到機場
Just get yourself to the airport.
其他事我會處理 知道了嗎？
I'll take care of everything else.
豹哥 你可能不知道
But Brother Bao, you don't understand.
現在狀況真的有一點亂
Things are a little messed up right now.
你就照我的話去做 不要想那麼多
Don't worry, just do what I said.
不是啦！ 豹哥        好！ 一路順風
-But Brother Bao... -Safe travels.
豹哥 等一下...
Brother Bao, wait...
怎麼啦？
What?
你看前面路
Hey, watch the road!
哈囉！ 您現在打的就是我阿洪的手機
Hello! You've reached Hong's cell phone.
真對不起 我現在不方便...
I'm sorry that I'm unable
to take your call...
喂 我豹哥啦！
Hey, this is Brother Bao.
你有看我那幾個孩子沒？
Have you seen my boys there tonight?
好好好
Okay.
安怎？
What?
走
Let's go!
走了 走了
Let's go, let's go.
不好意思 老闆娘
Excuse me, ma'am.
你剛才有看到幾個人走進來嗎？
Did you just see someone run in here?
休息三百
Quicky? Three hundred.
沒有要那個啦
Oh, we're not, uh...
若是要過夜八百
Eight hundred for the night.
好 謝謝
Okay, thanks.
那她知道你喜歡她嗎？
Does she know that you like her?
不知道
No.
為什麼？
Why not?
因為... 每次看到她我就很緊張
Because I get so nervous around her.
那你真的很喜歡她
So you must really like her.
嗯
Yeah.
那你要不要跟她說你很喜歡她
So why don't you tell her that you
like her?
嗯
Oh.
我有想過啦
I've thought about it.
我覺得喜歡一個人 是一件很美好的事情
I think being in love is
a beautiful thing.
要勇敢一點
But you have to be brave.
要抱著被拒絕的心態
And be prepared for rejection.
像個男人一樣
Like a man.
嗯
Oh.
嘿 阿洪
Hey, Hong.
拿到了嗎？
Did you get it?
拿到了
We got it.
阿洪 那我們先走囉
We're leaving now, Hong.
等一下 等一下
Hold on, hold on.
雖然這一次出了一點小狀況
Despite a few minor setbacks
我承認是我交代不夠清楚
And a little miscommunication
on my part.
但是我們這一票 真的做得非常漂亮
We still managed to make a sweet score.
很好 很好
Excellent.
嗯...
Oh...
阿洪 你真的已經很努力的啦
It was a good try, Hong.
嘿
Right.
你還是我們的阿洪
You're still our Hong.
對啊
Yeah.
你們三個土炮要去哪裡啊？
Where are you three morons going?
這事情沒意思啊
There's no point anymore.
對啦 這東西還給你啦
Oh yeah, you can have this back.
歹勢 阿洪
Sorry, Hong.
歹勢啦 阿洪
看什麼看？
What are you looking at?
好險喔
Close call.
有沒有？
Hear anything?
應該不是這間
It's probably not this one.
你小心一點
Hey, be careful.
你這裡等一下 我上去一下
Wait for me here.
賣面的
Hey, noodle boy.
這怎麼回事？
What is this?
豹哥給你這個幹什麼？
Why did Brother Bao give this to you?
我不知道啊
I don't know.
他不知道
He doesn't know.
是有人叫他幫忙帶去巴黎
Someone told him to bring it to Paris.
巴黎...？
Paris?
會不會痛？
Did that hurt?
不痛
No.
怎麼可能...
I don't believe it.
一定有
There has to be something.
你幹嘛？
What are you doing?
不要吵
Shut up.
欸 你幹嘛
Hey, what are you doing?
就不相信
Come on.
在哪裡？
Where is it?
法文課？ 什麼啊？
French lessons? What the hell?
沒道理啊
It makes no sense.
豹哥把他的照片給你
Brother Bao gave you his photo.
叫你帶去巴黎
To take to Paris...
那是豹哥？
That's Brother Bao?
你不要講話
Please be quiet.
你還是乖乖的告訴我 到底發生什麼事？
So tell me again what's really going on?
我不知道啦 真的啦
I don't know. Really.
阿洪
Hong.
二伯
Uncle.
你這孩子到底是在想什麼？
What's wrong with you kids?
怎麼講的話都不要聽
You don't listen to anything I say.
小凱
Kai
你不是乖乖的應該去機場了嗎？
Shouldn't you be on your way
to the airport?
你可以去巴黎啦
You can go to Paris now.
那是因為...
It's cause...
喔...
Oh...
你幹的好事啊
Nicely done!
二伯 我只是想說...
Uncle, I was just...
先干條大的 對吧
You wanted a big score, huh?
我告訴你 這麼重要的事情
You think I'd hand over
anything important
會交給這種菜烏嗎？
To this dipshit?
真正的貨我早就處理好了
I already took care of the real package.
警察！ 別動
Police! Freeze!
把槍放下
Put the gun down!
假的！
It's fake.
放下        放下
-Put it down! -Put it down!
假的
It's fake.
放下
Put it down.
啊
Huh.
走啊
Go!
學長 你沒事吧？
Sir, are you okay?
追追追
Go after them!
嘿
Hey!
我們怎麼辦啊？
What about us?
你手鬆得開嗎？
Can you get your hands free?
他好像沒有綁很緊
It's not tied too tightly.
你也可以試看看嗎？
Can you try?
好
Okay.
高高 來幫忙啦
Gao, come help!
喔
Oh.
可以嗎？
Did you get it?
你還好吧
Are you okay?
還好啊
I'm okay.
你們？
You guys?
事情都處理好了？
You take care of everything?
恁爸都要退休了
I'm supposed to be retiring.
還搞這款
No more of this shit.
我警告你喔！ 我什麼事情都沒有做
I'm telling you, I didn't do anything.
你現在要帶我去哪裡？
Where are you taking me now?
回警察局對不對？
Back to the station?
我也可以當警察
You know, I would make a good cop.
你覺得我去考警察怎麼樣？
What do you think?
我們現在要坐警車嗎？
Are we going in the cop car?
那我要坐前面
I want to ride shotgun.
喔 輕一點
Hey, take it easy.
你不上車嗎？
Aren't you coming?
學長 都跑走了
Sir, everyone's gone.
那些小鬼都不見了
No sign of the kids either.
我只找到這個
All I found was this.
上車！ 走囉
Come on, get in. Let's go.
那現在怎麼辦？
What should we do now?
我們要不要回房地產公司啊？
Go back to the real estate office?
哈囉？
Hello!
學長 你還好吧？
Sir, are you okay?
我沒事
I'm fine.
那我們上車啦 回去囉
Get in the car. Let's go.
那你飛機還趕得上嗎？
You have time to get to the airport?
喔 還可以啊
Oh, I think so.
欸 你們餓不餓？
Hey, are you guys hungry?
有一點
A little.
高高 要不要再去吃一點東西？
You want to get something to eat, Gao?
喔 不用 我好飽喔
Oh, no I'm stuffed.
啊？
Huh?
我該回去工作了 桃子還在店裡等我
I should head back,
Peach is waiting for me.
喔
Oh.
嘿 你抽到哪裡再跟我講
Hey, tell me where you get sent.
不要變笨
Take care.
好啦 那我走囉
Okay, I'm going now.
拜拜
Bye bye.
我都不知道已經這麼晚了
I didn't know it was so late already.
沒關係
It's okay.
我... 還是回家好了
I should go home anyway
可是你不是想吃東西嗎？
But I thought you were hungry.
是啊
Yeah...
可是真的有點晚了
But it's getting kind of late.
而且 你應該也差不多了吧
And...you should get going too.
欸 我知道吃什麼了
Hey, I know where we can go.
歡迎光臨
Hello and welcome.
桃子
Peach.
你不是說兩個小時嗎？
I thought you said only a few hours?
對不起啦
I'm sorry.
怎麼那麼久啊？
What took you so long?
喔 我剛剛遇到一點事情
I ran into a few problems.
那接下來兩班都給你代喔
Well, you're covering my next
two shifts.
好
Okay.
後面還有些貨還沒上
There's more stuff that needs
to be stocked.
好
Okay.
桃子
Peach.
嗯？
Hmm?
什麼？
What?
明天見
See you tomorrow.
嗯 高高 拜拜
Bye bye, Gao.
拜拜
Bye bye.
這裡是哪裡啊？
What is this place?
你等我一下
Give me a minute.
不好意思 沒有水餃了
Sorry, we're out of dumplings.
是喔
It's okay.
你這樣來得及嗎？
You sure you have time?
喔 還好
I think so.
待會再去樓上拿個東西就好了
I just have to grab my stuff upstairs.
還可以嗎？
How is it?
還不錯啊
Not bad.
你在笑什麼？
What are you smiling about?
沒有啊
Nothing.
你知道 你之前在書店的時候 快把我給煩死了
I was thinking about you bugging me
at the bookstore.
才沒有咧
Yeah right.
我只是隨便聊聊
You were just someone to talk to.
喔
Oh.
等我一下
Wait a second.
嗯 我...
So I...
那我...
I should...
蘇西
Susie